ELENA KRIVIN

Krivin.Elena@gmail.com 1 902-580-8287 Eastern Passage, NS

WEBSITES AND PORTFOLIOS

- https://elena-krivin.com
- http://linkedin.com/in/ElenaKrivin
- https://github.com/K-Lenka

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- Git
- SQL
- Figma
- React
- WebPack
- Node.js
- JQuery
- TypeScript
- WordPress
- Express
- MongoDB

COURSES

WEB PROGRAMMING WITH PYTHON AND JAVASCRIPT

HARVARDX CS50W Jul 2021-Nov 2021

WEB DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

SKILLSFORHIRE Apr 2021-Jul 2021

JS/FRONT-END DEVELOPER

RS SCHOOL Feb 2021-Jul 2021

WEB DEVELOPER

BOOTCAMP UDEMY Dec 2020

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Innovative and proactive Front End Web Developer bringing in-depth knowledge of latest technology trends to produce clean website design. Experience handling HTML and CSS coding, design and extensions to meet organization's front-facing internet needs. Exceptional team player with an analytical approach to developing useful solutions.

KEY SKILLS AND CHARACTERISTICS

- Ability to process large array of information in an accurate manner
- Strong communication skills
- Keen attention to detail, well organized and flexible
- Positive self-motivated and creative person
- Good team player

WORK EXPERIENCE

ACCOUNTING ASSISTANT

CABCO. Halifax, NS • Jan 2022 - Present

- Accounts Receivable, Accounts Payable, data verification, data entry, invoicing and collection.
- Responding to customer invoice inquiries and resolves issues in a timely manner.

FINANCE & ADMIN ASSISTAN

OFFICE INTERIORS. Halifax, NS • Jun 2020 - Nov 2020

- Reconciled account information and reported figures in general ledger by comparing to bank account statement each month.
- Processed accounts payable. Provided assistance with accounts receivable.

FURNITURE SALES COORDINATOR

OFFICE INTERIORS. Halifax, NS • Sep 2019 - Jun 2020

- Worked with Sales, Operations and Warehouse manager to ensure furniture orders are, placed and scheduled for installation.
- Processed and handled customer complaints, answering questions and providing alternative solutions.

FREELANCER

UTEST. Framingham, Massachusetts • Mar 2019 – Oct 2019

- Tested mobile applications, providing feedbacks and writing effective test reports.
- Analyzed the scope for a test cycle, reviewing all related material provided by the customer and clearly understanding the testing objectives.

ADMINISTRATIVE SUPPORT

TENDO IL. Tel-Aviv, Israel[®] Mar – Dec 2018

- Checked document compliance, processed, verified and recorded financial documents and forms, assisted with financial refund processing. Performed minor accounting functions and data entry.
- Processed outgoing wire transfers and credit card payments.

PRODUCTION ORDER PLANNING AND HANDLING SPECIALIST

ALFA LAVAL POTOK. Moscow, Russia • Jan 2016 - Nov 2016

- Monitored the execution and quality assurance of equipment on time.
- Scheduled and coordinated orders from Sales Department. Registered incoming orders in Jeeves.

ORDER COORDINATOR

ALFA LAVAL POTOK. Moscow, Russia • Aug 2011 – Jan 2016

- Created shipping and invoicing documents with accurate customer, destination and materials information to meet shipper standards and identify any hazardous contents.
- Assisted customers by providing tracking information and resolving shipping or merchandise issues.

WAREHOUSE ADMINISTRATOR

ALFA LAVAL POTOK. Moscow, Russia • Jul 2008 - Aug 2011

- Kept documentation and records accurate and up-to-date with latest data to prevent errors in processing or delivery.
- Boosted warehouse operations performance by overseeing dispatching and setting optimal employee schedules.

VOLUNTEERING

CANADIAN EVALUATION SOCIETY. Halifax, NS • May 2019

- Visitor orientation during events.
- Administrative support, video editing for event .

EDUCATION

MASTER'S DEGREE IN QUALITY MANAGEMENT • 2003 – 2008 Korolev, Russia

Korolev Institute of Management, Economics and Sociology. **SPECIALTY**: Quality management, engineering and technology.